imhv.com 2015-05-24

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://imhv.com/contact.php).

Last Updated: April 10, 2015

imhv.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. 

At imhv.com, we use the "Privacy by Design" approach. This means that we think of privacy implication before building a new feature, we don't ask for information we don't need, and we protect the information we have.

We take pride in treating our users' privacy the way we'd like to be treated by a website like imhv.com, as individuals.

 _We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period._

**

## Data Collected

**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided.

For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase.

You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site.

Like most Web sites, imhv.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. 

For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider, your IP address or use cookie or clear GIF technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit.

We also collect information about how you use this website (including demographic information), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, which pages you visited throughout our site, and other technical information.

We may collect this information through services such as **Google Analytics** or other web analytics platform.

You may disable Google Analytics by visiting [Google's Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=Aci0TCiRDcnrXrdffABE6Nifr9QppTwHkj_NTB8gd0FaMd9YV_wg5YIp3OvYIp-y-pdTWNhIhLjQXh6TyIek2jcL233J8XokduMKuR1N-zHOJP2Ls6zIAM_wKkwTu-xTmML-Aucg-KsrCOB6oLAL11n-sPX9rEefGBMsmC7iVBTJsDKZmWkr3jnzCeVGR-wzwiV8cGO96yfR&hl=en).

And we also collect information that you choose send to us (including website messages, blog comments, emails).

Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site.

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means.

In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences.

**

## Use Of Data

**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to develop and manage this website, enhance your visit, provide you web services, send to you your purchased products, services, statements and invoices, deliver more individualized content and advertising and send you marketing communications.

 _We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone._

**Aggregated Informatio** n (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways.

For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive).

Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners.

Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on imhv.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by imhv.com and other topics we think you might find of interest. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by imhv.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, tracking and improving the effectiveness of our advertising, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you.

Certain third parties who manage or provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) or our newsletter (our Mailing list server provider provider for example) may access such information.

Our mailing list server provider is Getresponse.com. Therefore, the information you provide can be accessed by those who manage our mailing lists and newsletters at Getresponse.com. You can read Getresponse's Anti-Spam Policy [here](http://www.getresponse.com/legal/antispam.html). 

_We will use your information only as permitted by law._

In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses.

In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.

We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary.

Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

## Remarketing Program

We may use third-party cookies as part of remarketing activities we conduct with **Google Adwords** and/or other third-party vendors (For example SiteScout or Adroll), to help provide you with relevant promotional offers as you use the Internet.

As part of these remarketing activities, these third-party cookies may record your visits to our Websites and web sites visited prior to using our Websites.

Such cookies can then be used to serve advertisements to you on other web sites.

You may choose to be exempt from the use of Google remarketing cookies at the [Google advertising privacy page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin).

Alternatively, you may opt-out of remarketing on the Google network and similar networks at the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Opting out will not prevent advertisements from being served to you on the Internet; it will only affect advertisements that utilize remarketing cookies to serve advertisements on the specified advertising networks.

We are not responsible for the activities of other parties that may not comply with your opt-out requests.

**

## Third Party Sites And Advertisements

**

imhv.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. 

Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a imhv.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.

Also, through imhv.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. 

imhv.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you.

For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. 

Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information.

imhv.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of imhv.com and this policy.

**

## Children

**

imhv.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. 

If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe imhv.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

## Contacting Us

We can be reached through this page: <http://imhv.com/contact.php>

## Changes to this Policy

imhv.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. 

Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**

## Governing law

**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Hungary law.

If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Hungary.

Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Hungary.

Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

imhv.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Hungary.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
